A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Estate Files, Accession 2009:053 FA1374
Rockefeller Archive Center
Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Estate Files, Accession 2009:053
1994-2008
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
FA1374
2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes.
Scope and Contents
Records primarily document Woodstock Foundation, the Woodstock Inn and Resort, Billings Farm and Museum, Caneel Bay, and other properties.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
As received.
- Open Space Institute - General (Box 1)
- Open Space Institute - Debt Reorganization (Box 1)
- Open Space Institute - Englewood Lakes - Sales Agreement (Box 1)
- Open Space Institute - Englewood Lakes - TCF Plan (Box 1)
- Woodstock Community Fund - General (Box 1)
- Woodstock Community Fund - Parking Study (Box 1)
- Woodstock Foundation - Governor' s Conference on Cultural Heritage Tourism (Box 1)
- Woodstock Foundation - LSR Conservation Award, 1996-1998 (Box 1)
- Woodstock Foundation - MPNHP/Endowment Fund (Box 1)
- Woodstock Foundation - National Geographic Proposal (Box 1)
- Woodstock Foundation - Transfer of Billings Farm and Museum (Box 1)
- Woodstock Foundation - The "Vermont Brand" (Box 1)
- Woodstock Foundation - Writing Project/LSR Contribution to Woodstock (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Including: Muller, H.N.
- Woodstock/LSR Property Planning (Box 1)
- Billings Farm and Museum - General, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Billings Farm and Museum - Collections and Accreditation (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Billings Farm and Museum - Condemnation Rights (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Billings Farm and Museum - Corkum Property (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Billings Farm and Museum - Exhibit Reinstallation (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Billings Farm and Museum - Historical Narrative, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Billings Farm and Museum - Member Survey (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Billings Farm and Museum - Registered Trade Names (Box 2, Folder 8)
- LSR Intervivos Trust - General, 1998-2008 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- LSR Intervivos Trust - David A. Donath/Housing Option (Box 2, Folder 10)
- LSR Intervivos Trust - Howe House/Expenses (Box 2, Folder 11)
- LSR Intervivos Trust - Rockefeller Trust Co./Agency Agreement (Box 2, Folder 12)
- LSR Intervivos Trust - Sherman Howe Property Purchase (Box 2, Folder 13)
- LSR Fund/Art Gifts - Modigliani/General and Appraisal (Box 2, Folder 14)
- LSR Fund/Art Gifts - Modigliani/Certificate and Insurance (Box 2, Folder 15)
- MSKCC/Marks Proposal/LSR Letter - Research Program for Translational and Integrative Medicine (Box 2, Folder 16)
- U.S. Virgin Islands/Caneel Bay - General/Retained Use Estate (Box 2, Folder 17)
- U.S. Virgin Islands/Caneel Bay - LSR Letter (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Woodstock Resort Corporation - Woodstock Inn and Resort (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Woodstock Resort Corporation - Miscellaneous Properties and Appraisals - 106 Parcel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Woodstock Resort Corporation - Miscellaneous Properties and Appraisals - Bassett Farm RFR, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Woodstock Resort Corporation - Miscellaneous Properties and Appraisals - Blake Hill, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Woodstock Resort Corporation - Miscellaneous Properties and Appraisals - Frost Mill Planning, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Woodstock Resort Corporation - Miscellaneous Properties and Appraisals - Floyd Hall House, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)